No matter where life takes you, always keep swingin'
Everyone's Hero is a adventure, animation, comedy film directed by Colin Brady.
A boy begins a grand journey to return Babe Ruth's baseball bat before the
deciding game of the 1932 World Series comes to a close.
Yankee Irving (voice), played by Jake T. Austin.
Screwie (voice), played by Rob Reiner.
Lefty Maginnis (voice), played by William H. Macy.
Stanley Irving (voice), played by Mandy Patinkin.
Hobo Andy / Maitre D' (voice), played by Richard Kind.
Mr. Robinson (voice), played by Robert Wagner.
Everyone's Hero is a 2006 American animated sports comedy
film directed by Christopher Reeve, Daniel St.
Pierre and Colin Brady.
Starring Jake T.
Austin, Rob Reiner, William H.
Macy, Raven-Symoné and Whoopi Goldberg, along with many others.
The film was produced by IDT Entertainment in Toronto with portions outsourced to Reel FX
Creative Studios and was distributed domestically by 20th Century Fox.
The film was theatrically released on September 15, 2006, to mixed reviews from critics
and was a financial flop, earning $16.6 million on a $35 million budget.
It also marked the final film for Dana Reeve before her death in March 2006, six months before the release of
the film; it was dedicated to her and her husband, Christopher Reeve, who co-directed the film.
The film explores themes of sports, baseball, villain, baseball bat, theft.
The tone is lighthearted.